<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on IoT On The Edge</title>
    <link>https://petriok.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on IoT On The Edge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 12:32:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://petriok.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Development Board</title>
      <link>https://petriok.github.io/posts/custom-development-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 12:32:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petriok.github.io/posts/custom-development-board/</guid>
      <description>Making PCBs Long gone are the days when manufacturing your own PCB was either expensive or tedious. A long time ago I wanted to make my own PCBs and acquired the materials and tooling for it. I needed to print the traces on a transparent film paper, buy photoresist PCBs, UV exposure, etching with Ferric Chloride (with a heater), cleaning, drilling and so on. I did a few PCBs but the end result wasn&amp;rsquo;t that pretty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TensorFlow Lite on Cortex M7</title>
      <link>https://petriok.github.io/posts/tflite-on-cortex-m7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 17:23:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petriok.github.io/posts/tflite-on-cortex-m7/</guid>
      <description>Just a brief note I have been too busy to dive deep on to analyzing the performance of the TensorFlow Lite micro, but as I already did some prep work I&amp;rsquo;ll just post what I did. My intention still is to take the plunge to the inner workings of TFLite, hopefully sooner than later.
This post is just a quick follow up to compare TFLite micro to STMCubeAI which I was testing on the previous post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STM CubeAI on Cortex M7</title>
      <link>https://petriok.github.io/posts/stm-cubeai-on-cortex-m7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 22:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petriok.github.io/posts/stm-cubeai-on-cortex-m7/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This post is a brief performance analysis for running machine learning inference (prediction) on a Cortex-M7 microcontroller. I will concentrate here on the micro-optimizations by inspecting the code at assembly level.
The trained model is borrowed from the benchmarks done by Stupid Projects and adapted to my setup.
Test setup The MCU under test is an STM32H7 with 2MBytes of flash and 1MByte RAM, running at 480MHz. For an embedded microcontroller, this is truly a high-end device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>